-------------------------------------
Aya Shameimaru - Incident Zero version
for MUGEN
-------------------------------------
Author: RicePigeon

=========================================
10/31/2020 - Version 2020.10.31
=========================================

- [System] Fixed bug where Projectiles were not adding Power or Spirit in Type-ß.
- [System] Fixed graphical bug in Alignment/Palette selector.
- [System] Fixed minor positioning error in ground tech state.
- Crush Attack: Damage now affected by proration.
- 2z: Hit velocity on block increased.
- Throw: Fixed Ikemen-exclusive bugs.
- Throw: Remove facep2 & fall parameter from throw hitdef.

=========================================
04/16/2020 - Version 2020.04.16
=========================================

- [System] Fixed hitvel bug involving y acceleration.
- [System] Fixed tick fix code in CMD file.
- [System] Fixed minor graphical bug involving Spellcard text.
- [System] Fall Recovertime values adjusted to compensate for recently discovered engine bug.
- [System] Fixed bug involving corner wallbounces.
- [System] Type-A and Type-B alignments have been merged into a single new alignment called Type-α. Type-C has been renamed Type-ß.
- [System] Foward dashing during Type-α now behaves the same as the former Type-B. Grazing removed.
- [System] Type-α Spirit meter from taking damage increased (33%->50%).
- [System] Normals now deal chip damage during Type-α.
- [System] Just Defend: Now usable regardless of alignment.
- [System] Last Word minimum damage scaling increased (30%->50%).
- [System] Type-ß alignment now scales all damage by 80%. Damage reduction during Spell Overdrive removed.
- Guard Cancel: Can now be used by any alignments. Now costs 1000 Power instead of 25% Spirit.
- Guard Cancel: Fixed bug that erroneously allowed Guard Cancels to gain Counterhit properties.
- Dash Cancel: Now always costs 50% Spirit, regardless of whether Spell Overdrive is active.
- Spell Rage: Removed.
- Throw: Now has 2f of startup.
- 5y: Is now jump cancellable.
- Tengu Drum: Adjusted recoil velocity after successful hit.
- Tengu Felling: Damage increased (90->100), hitbox size increased.
- "Illusionary Dominance": Total damage increased: (445->556).

=========================================
06/23/2019 - Version 2019.06.23
=========================================

- [System] Characters in the Type-C alignment can now cancel Spellcards into other Spellcards, at an additional proration.
- [System] Minor adjustments to hurtboxes in some gethit states.
- [System] Added compatibility with Suwako_THIZ's Blighted Earth effects.
- [System] Corrected Wallbounce & Groundbounce behaviors.
- [System] Adjusted how the character handles landing sounds in certain basic states.
- [System] Fixed IKEMEN exclusive visual issue where certain effect helpers would incorrectly generate a shadow.
- Spell Trance: Now consumes 100% Spirit, Power requirement reduced (2000->1000).
- Spell Trance: Last Words no longer require Spirit while Spell Trance is active.
- Spell Overdrive: Now gives a 50% velocity increase to walk & dashing.
- Spell Overdrive: Now allows Specials to be cancelled into another Special once per chain.

=========================================
05/05/2019 - Version 2019.05.05
=========================================

- First release.

------------------
Contents
------------------

1. Contents (You're reading this)
2. System Mechanics
3. Move List
   - Notable Moves
   - Specials & Supers
   - Spellcards
4. Special Thanks

----------
Moves
----------

F - Toward
B - Back
U - Up
D - Down

x - Weak Attack
y - Medium Attack
z - Strong Attack
a - Unique Skill
b - Bombs/Special Actions
c - Shortcut for X+Y+Z

Start - Taunt


----------------
System Mechanics
----------------

* Type-α alignment causes all Normals & Command Normals to deal non-KO-able chip damage.
* Type-ß alignment scales all damage done by 80%.

* Hold x/y/z - Safe Fall [Ground] / Air Tech [Air].
- Recovers quickly after being knocked down. Hold Back or Forward to tech in that direction. Cannot Safe Fall/Tech any moves that cause 
  a Hard Knockdown.

* 1, 4, or 7 - Just Defend

* 412b - Guard Cancel [G]
- Counterattack. Requires 1000 Power, can only be done during blockstun.

* 5b - Bomb [G] (Type-α Only)
- Requires 100% Spirit.

* 236b - Crush Attack (Type-α Only)
- Requires 500 Power. Causes a knockdown on hit, causes a guard crush if blocked.

* X+Y+Z - Spell Trance [G] (Type-α Only)
- Requires 2000 Power. Allows unlimited use of Spellcards for a limited time. Ends when Last Word is used.

* 5b - Dash Cancel (Type-ß Only)
- Requires 50% Spirit, can only be done on successful hit. Cancels current action into a forward dash.

* X+Y+Z - Spell Overdrive [G] (Type-ß Only)
- Requires 1000 Power. Allows all grounded Normals to be jump cancelled and allows chaining from Medium into Heavy Normals. Ends when
  any Spellcard is used.

--------------
Notable moves
--------------

Jump Cancellable Normals: 5y

Unique Skill: Bunbunmaru Photoshoot
- Pressing A will cause Aya to take out her camera and take a picture to stun the opponent. The crosshairs determine the placement
  of the hitbox, but will cause no damage. Holding A will allow the crosshairs to be controlled. Can only be used if Aya's camera
  gauge is at 100%. Can be cancelled into from Aya's Specials.

* F,F or B,B: Dash/Air Dash
- Does a forward or backward dash. Forward Dash behavior differs in Type-B alignment and gains graze properties. Can double air dash
  during Type-C alignment.

* F+z or B+z - Throw [GA]
- Aya's throw. Can hit opponents in hitstun, but not blockstun. Using a throw during a combo gives the opponent additional
  time to throw escape.

* DB+Z (1z) - [G]
- Aya does an overhead smack.

* j.D+z (j.2z) - [A]
- Aya does a divekick.

-----------------
Specials & Supers
-----------------


Note: Each move indicates if it can be done on the ground only [G], in the air only [A], or both [GA]

* D,DF,F + X/Y/Z (236X, 236Y, & 236Z) - Gust Fan [GA]
- Aya swipes her fan, firing a wind projectile. Button press determines speed.

* Hold B,F + X/Y/Z ([4]6X, [4]6Y, & [4]6Z) - Dominating Dash [GA]
- Aya thrusts forward surrounded by wind. Passes through the opponent.

* Hold D,U + X/Y/Z ([2]8X, [2]8Y, & [2]8Z) - Tengu Drum [G]
- Aya leaps forward and lands on her opponent. Hits overhead. Has two potential follow-ups. Holding Back or Forward after hit will
  allow Aya to alter the trajectory of her descent.       

* X/Y/Z (During Tengu Drum, before hit) - Tengu's Downburst [A]
- Aya does a mid-air reversal, cancelling prematurely out of Tengu Drum to do a divekick.

* X/Y/Z (During Tengu Drum, after hit) - Tengu Felling [A]
- Aya follows up the headstomp portion of Tengu Drum with a blast of wind and knocks the opponent back a bit.


-----------------------------
Spellcards
-----------------------------

* D,DF,F,D,DF,F + X/Y/Z (236236X, 236236Y, & 236236Z) - Wind Sign "Wind of the Tengu Path" [GA]
- Aya launches a horizontal blast of wind that hits multiple times. Low damage, but is quick enough to allow Aya to follow
  up afterward.

* Hold B,F,B,F + X/Y/Z ([4]646X, [4]646Y, & [4]646Z) - Squall "Sarutahiko's Guidance" [GA]
- Effectively an upgrade of Dominating Dash; Aya rushes even quicker past her opponent. Possesses projectile invincibility
  throughout the entire dash portion.

* Hold DB,DF,DB,U + X/Y/Z ([1]318X, [1]318Y, & [1]318Z) - Tornado "Indication to the Divine" [G]
- Reversal. Aya summons a tornado around her that extends upward. Unsafe on block, but allows Aya to follow up after the 
  final hit.

-----------------------------
Last Word Spellcards
-----------------------------

Note 1: In Type-α, Last Words can only be performed during Spell Trance, and requires 100% Spirit. Ends Spell Trance on use.
Note 2: Last Words cannot be used during Type-ß.

* Hold B,F,B,F + B ([4]646b) - "Illusionary Dominance" [G Only]
- Aya rushes at an upward angle. On successful contact, Aya will continue to repeatedly rush the opponent before stomping them
  into the ground.

---------------
Special Thanks:
---------------

Elecbyte 		- For making MUGEN and making all kinds of fantasy fights possible.
ZUN & Tasofro		- Touhou much?
Necromancer		- His/Her code archive
P.o.t.S.		- Original damage dampening code, revised Parry code
Jmorphman & JustNoPoint	- Explodsive buffering system
Daiya			- Portraits


Sprite & Palette submissions:
- Darkflare
- Nep Heart
- PlasmoidThunder
- Kohaku

Testers:
- 

And anyone else I forgot to mention
