-------------------------------------
Suwako Moriya - Incident Zero version
for MUGEN
-------------------------------------
Author: RicePigeon

=========================================
10/31/2020 - Version 2020.10.31
=========================================

- [System] Fixed graphical bug in Alignment/Palette selector.
- [System] Fixed minor positioning error in ground tech state.
- [System] Fixed bug where projectiles were not adding Power or Spirit in Type-ß.
- [System] Fixed bug where Type-ß Suwako was not gaining Spirit when walking forward.
- Crush Attack: Damage now affected by proration.
- 2z: Hit velocity on block increased.
- Throw/Air Throw: Tech window increased (8f/16f->15f/27f).
- Throw/Air Throw: Fixed Ikemen-exclusive bugs.

=========================================
04/18/2020 - Version 2020.04.18
=========================================

- [System] Fixed tick fix code in CMD file.
- [System] Fixed minor graphical bug involving Spellcard text.
- [System] Fall Recovertime values adjusted to compensate for recently discovered engine bug.
- [System] Fixed bug involving corner wallbounces.
- [System] Type-A and Type-B alignments have been merged into a single new alignment called Type-α. Type-C has been renamed Type-ß.
- [System] Foward dashing during Type-α now behaves the same as the former Type-B. Grazing removed.
- [System] Type-α Spirit meter from taking damage increased (33%->50%).
- [System] Normals now deal chip damage during Type-α.
- [System] Just Defend: Now usable regardless of alignment.
- [System] Last Word minimum damage scaling increased (30%->50%).
- [System] Type-ß alignment now scales all damage by 80%. Damage reduction during Spell Overdrive removed.
- Guard Cancel: Can now be used by any alignments. Now costs 1000 Power instead of 25% Spirit.
- Guard Cancel: Fixed bug that erroneously allowed Guard Cancels to gain Counterhit properties.
- Dash Cancel: Now always costs 50% Spirit, regardless of whether Spell Overdrive is active.
- Spell Rage: Removed.
- Throw: Now has 2f of startup.
- 5z: Is now jump cancellable.
- 2x: Is now jump cancellable.
- Air Throw added.
- "Mr. Mishaguji": Total Damage increased (544->594).

=========================================
06/20/2019 - Version 2019.06.20
=========================================

- First release.

------------------
Contents
------------------

1. Contents (You're reading this)
2. System Mechanics
3. Move List
   - Notable Moves
   - Specials & Supers
   - Spellcards
4. Special Thanks

----------
Moves
----------

F - Toward
B - Back
U - Up
D - Down

x - Weak Attack
y - Medium Attack
z - Strong Attack
a - Unique Skill
b - Bombs/Special Actions
c - Shortcut for X+Y+Z

Start - Taunt


----------------
System Mechanics
----------------

* Type-α alignment causes all Normals & Command Normals to deal non-KO-able chip damage.
* Type-ß alignment scales all damage done by 80%.

* Hold x/y/z - Safe Fall [Ground] / Air Tech [Air].
- Recovers quickly after being knocked down. Hold Back or Forward to tech in that direction. Cannot Safe Fall/Tech any moves that cause 
  a Hard Knockdown.

* 1, 4, or 7 - Just Defend

* 412x/y/z - Guard Cancel [G]
- Counterattack. Requires 1000 Power, can only be done during blockstun.

* 5b - Bomb [G] (Type-α Only)
- Requires 100% Spirit.

* 236b - Crush Attack (Type-α Only)
- Requires 500 Power. Causes a knockdown on hit, causes a guard crush if blocked.

* X+Y+Z - Spell Trance [G] (Type-α Only)
- Requires 1000 Power and 100% Spirit. Allows unlimited use of Spellcards for a limited time. Ends when Last Word is used.

* 5b - Dash Cancel (Type-ß Only)
- Requires 50% Spirit, can only be done on successful hit. Cancels current action into a forward dash.

* X+Y+Z - Spell Overdrive [G] (Type-ß Only)
- Requires 1000 Power. Allows all grounded Normals to be jump cancelled and allows chaining from Medium into Heavy Normals. Allows Specials
  to be cancelled into another Special once per chain. Ends when any Spellcard is used.

--------------
Notable moves
--------------

Jump Cancellable Normals (Yin Stance): 5z, 2x

Unique Skill: Toad in the Hole
- Places Suwako in an underground state, or returns her to the surface if she is already underground. Suwako can move freely, but
  is unable to block.

* F,F or B,B: Dash/Air Dash
- Does a forward or backward dash. Forward Dash behavior differs in Type-B alignment and gains graze properties. Can double air dash
  during Type-C alignment.

* F+z or B+z - Throw [G]
- Suwako's throw. Can hit opponents in hitstun, but not blockstun. Using a throw during a combo gives the opponent additional
  time to throw escape.

* DF+Z (3z) - [G]
- Suwako leaps off her lilypad for an overhead attack.

* j.D+z (j.2z) - [A]
- Suwako immediately returns to the ground and leaps forward.

-----------------
Specials & Supers
-----------------


Note: Each move indicates if it can be done on the ground only [G], in the air only [A], or both [GA]. Moves denoted with [U] can be used
while Underground.

* D,DF,F + X/Y/Z (236X, 236Y, & 236Z) - Stone Frog God [GU]
- Suwako rides a giant stone frog that hits OTG. Button press determines startup and distance travelled.

* D,DF,F + X/Y/Z (236X, 236Y, & 236Z) - Ancient Iron Ring [A]
- Suwako spins her metal ring above her as she glides forward. Button press determines distance and number of hits.

* F,D,DF + X/Y/Z (623X, 623Y, & 623Z) - Toad God [G]
- Suwako surrounds herself in purple energy, causing a wallbounce on the hit hit.     

* D,D + X/Y/Z (22X, 22Y, & 22Z) - Blighted Earth [G]
- Suwako summons a cloud of black mist centered at her location. If a compatible opponent steps inside, they will continuously take
  damage. Button press determines both the size of the mist cloud and amount of damage dealt over time. Lasts 5 seconds or until
  Suwako is hit.

* D,DB,B + X/Y/Z (214X, 214Y, & 214Z) - Ancient Geyser [GU]
- Projectile. Suwako rides a geyser upward. Button press determines number of hits and distance travelled. Suwako can cancel into a dash
  at the peak of the ascent.


-----------------------------
Spellcards
-----------------------------

Note: Spellcards in the Type-ß Alignment can be cancelled into another Spellcard, at the expense of additional proration.

* D,DF,F,D,DF,F + X/Y/Z (236236X, 236236Y, & 236236Z) - Divine Instrument "Moriya's Iron Ring" [GAU]
- Suwako throws her trademark iron ring, which bounces around the stage. Button press determines the initial angle of the ring. 
  Disappears if Suwako is hit. 

* D,DB,B,D,DB,B + X/Y/Z (214214X, 214214Y, & 214214Z) - Native God "Moriya God" [G]
- Suwako surrounds herself with a large cage of energy. Has startup invincibility.

-----------------------------
Last Word Spellcards
-----------------------------

Note 1: In Type-α, Last Words can only be performed during Spell Trance, and requires 100% Spirit. Ends Spell Trance on use.
Note 2: Last Words cannot be used during Type-ß.

* D,D,D + B (222b) - "Mr. Mishaguchi" [G Only]
- Suwako summons a crawling mist of dark energy that, upon contact, causes Suwako to summon the Mishaguchi scourge gods to strike
  the opponent. Unblockable, but has very limited vertical range.

---------------
Special Thanks:
---------------

Elecbyte 		- For making MUGEN and making all kinds of fantasy fights possible.
ZUN & Tasofro		- Touhou much?
Necromancer		- His/Her code archive
P.o.t.S.		- Original damage dampening code, revised Parry code
Jmorphman & JustNoPoint	- Explodsive buffering system
Daiya			- Portraits

Sprite & Palette submissions:
- 

Testers:
- 

And anyone else I forgot to mention
